Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Yale School of Drama, circa 1971-1999; Accession 2001-A-006
  - Lloyd Richard's Files
    - Rep II "A Raisin in the Sun", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1038)
    - RSVP to "A Raisin...Event", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1039)
    - Rep III "Richard II", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1040)
    - Winterfest, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1042)
    - Winterfest, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1043)
    - Winterfest, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1044)
    - "The Day of the Picnic", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1045)
    - "The Day of the Picnic", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1046)
    - "The Sweet Life", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1047)
    - "Chopin in Space", 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1048)
    - "Chopin in Space", Bosakowski, Phil, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1049)
    - Public Broadcasting Service
      - Memos to Station Managers, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1051)
      - Board of Directors: General, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1052)
      - Board and Membership Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1053)
      - Letters to Lloyd Richards as General Director, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1054)
      - Program Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1055)
      - Report to Managers, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1056)
    - Hip Pocket Musicals, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1057)
    - M Misc., 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1058)
    - N Misc., 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1059)
    - National Broadcasting Company TV, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1061)
    - New York Times Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1062)
    - National Council on the Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1063)
    - National Student Aid Coalition: F. Keppel, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1064)
    - National Public Radio, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1065)
    - National Public Television, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1066)
    - National Theatre Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1067)
    - Negro Ensemble, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1068)
    - New Drama Forum Association, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1069)
    - New Dramatists, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1070)
    - New Federal Theatre: Woodie King Jr., 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1071)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)
      - Artist in School Program, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1072)
      - Directing Intern Program, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1073)
      - Directing Fellows, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1074)
      - Handicapped Regulations (504), 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1075)
      - Director: F. Hodsoll, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1076)
      - Intermediate Theatre Panel, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1078)
      - National Partnership Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1079)
      - Policy Panel Media Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1080)
      - Report of the Directors, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1081)
      - Theatre Program, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1082)
      - Theatre Policy Panel, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1083)
    - Rep V "Night is Mother to the Day", 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1084)
    - Night and Day, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1085)
    - Night and Day, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1086)
    - O Misc., 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1087)
    - Eugene O'Neill
      - National Playwrights Conference C.A.R.I.B.U.S.T.E., 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1088)
      - Creative Arts in Education, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1089)
      - Board of Project Directors, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1090)
      - Rockefeller, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1092)
      - NEA, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1093)
      - Development, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1094)
      - Bellagio Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1095)
      - Executive Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1097)
      - Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 1098)
      - Quarterly Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1100)
      - Monte Cristo Cottage, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1101)
      - National Playwrights Conference Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1102)
      - NPC Second Step, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1103)
      - NPC Staff Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 1104)
      - NTI, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1105)
      - National Critics Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1106)
      - National Theatre for the Deaf, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1108)
      - National Playwrights Conference: Exxon Luncheon, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1110)
      - National Playwrights Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 1111)
    - P Misc., 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1113)
    - Public Broadcasting Service
      - PBS, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1114)
      - 1983 Apr (Box 24, Folder 1115)
      - Executive Committee, 1983 March 23 (Box 24, Folder 1116)
      - Executive Committee, 1983 December 7 (Box 24, Folder 1117)
      - Board of Directors (Box 24, Folder 1118)
    - Development: Cole Porter, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1119)
      - Carnegie Hall - Salute to Cole Porter, 1985 May 20 (Box 25, Folder 1120)
      - Yale School of Drama Benefit, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1122)
    - C, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1123)
    - D, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1124)
    - E, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1125)
    - F, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1126)
    - G, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1127)
    - H, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1128)
    - I, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1129)
    - J, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1130)
    - K, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1131)
    - L, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1132)
    - Long Wharf Theatre, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1133)
    - M, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1134)
    - N, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1135)
    - O, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1136)
    - P, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1137)
    - Q, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1138)
    - R, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1139)
  - CCA Grant Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1140)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)
    - Training
      - 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1141)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1142)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1143)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1144)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1145)
    - Large Theatre Grant
      - 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1146)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1147)
    - Evaluation (Box 26, Folder 1148)
    - Presenting Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1149)
    - Special Projects
      - "Warrior Ant", 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1150)
      - "Ivanov", 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1151)
    - Presenting Grant TJL, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1152)
    - Theatre Magazine Grants (Box 26, Folder 1153)
      - Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1154)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1155)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1156)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1157)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1158)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1159)
      - Translation Grant, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1160)
      - Services to the Field, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1161)
    - Info and Worksheets through April for, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1162)
    - Grants
      - 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1163)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1164)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1165)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1166)
  - Connecticut Commission LRP, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1167)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Humanities (Box 26, Folder 1168)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Humanities: "Ivanov" grant (Box 26, Folder 1169)
  - TCG
    - Royalty Survey (Box 26, Folder 1171)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1172)
    - Managers Bulletin (Box 26, Folder 1173)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts
    - Management Conference (Box 26, Folder 1175)
    - "Warrior Ant" Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1176)
    - Medea--A Blues Opera (Box 26, Folder 1177)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1178)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1179)
    - Applications and Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1180)
    - Three Year Applications, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1181)
  - Yale Cabaret
    - June Final Balances, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1182)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1183)
    - Correspondence and Clippings (Box 27, Folder 1184)
    - General (Box 27, Folder 1185)
    - Financials (Box 27, Folder 1186)
    - Membership
      - Originals: Brochures (Box 27, Folder 1187)
      - List of Members, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1188)
      - General (Box 27, Folder 1189)
    - Productions
      - "The Resurrection of Davvy Lee Cruthers" by Kerry Kennedy, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1190)
      - "Straight to Helms!" (Box 27, Folder 1191)
      - "Zastrozzi" By George F.Walker (Box 27, Folder 1192)
      - "The Sound of a Voice" (Box 27, Folder 1193)
      - "The Mystery of Irma Vep" by Charles Ludlam (Box 27, Folder 1194)
      - "Go On" by Nina Sadur" (Box 27, Folder 1195)
      - "The Lesson" by Eugene Ionesco (Box 27, Folder 1196)
      - "Miss Henrietta Stralson" by Joshua Fardon (Box 27, Folder 1197)
      - "X-Mas Special" (Box 27, Folder 1198)
      - "Thank You, Ladies and Gentleman" (Box 27, Folder 1199)
      - "Dybbuk" by Bruce Myers adapted from Saul Ansky's play (Box 27, Folder 1200)
      - "Live War Tonite" a collection of sketches, scenes etc (Box 27, Folder 1201)
      - "Dutchman" by Leroi Jones (Box 27, Folder 1202)
      - "Lovers" Brian Friel (Box 27, Folder 1203)
      - "Whatever happened to the 12 Dancing Princesses" (Box 27, Folder 1204)
      - "Plays of Silence" (Mountain, Language, On for the Road and Tomorrow's News) (Box 27, Folder 1205)
      - Yale Rep Press Features Season, General--For Specific Shows (Box 27, Folder 1206)
      - "Celina or The Child of Mystery" (Box 27, Folder 1207)
      - "Return of the Flaming Carrot" (Box 27, Folder 1208)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1209)
    - FY 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 1210 - 1211)
    - Dimmers Purchased, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1212)
    - Cabaret, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1213)
    - Work (Box 27, Folder 1214)
    - Revised Budget and Weekly Reports (Box 27, Folder 1215)
  - Press and Marketing Press Clippings
    - Press Releases, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1216)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Features Vol. 1, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 1217)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Features Vol. 2, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 1218)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1219)
    - Clips Rep Shows on Tour National Papers-Rep, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1220)
    - Yale Repertory Out of Town Features, Ads, Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1222)
    - Yale Rep Features, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1223)
    - Season Features, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1224 - 1226)
    - Advertising, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1227)
    - Tape D27: "Namibia--In God's Country" (Tape 1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1228)
    - Yale Rep Press Features Season, vol. 2, By Show, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1229)
    - Yale Rep Press Reviews Season, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1230)
    - Yale Rep Press Reviews Season vol. 2, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1231)
    - Advertising, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1232)
    - Yale Rep Press Reviews Season, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1233)
    - Yale Rep Press Features Season vol. 1, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1234 - 1235)
    - Advertisements, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1236)
    - Yale Rep Press Features, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1237)
    - Yale Rep Press Reviews, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 1238 - 1239)
    - Yale Rep Advertisements, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 1240)
    - Yale Rep Press Features, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 1241)
    - Advertisements Season, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1242)
    - Yale Rep Press Features Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1243)
    - Yale Rep Press Reviews, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1244)
    - Yale Rep Theatre Production History (Box 35, Folder 1245)
    - DAF Giving History, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 1246)
    - Fences (Box 35, Folder 1247)
    - "The Piano Lesson" Reviews: Los Angeles and Washington D.C. (Box 35, Folder 1248)
    - "The Piano Lesson" Clippings: New York Reviews, Pulitzer Prize and Tony Awards (Box 35, Folder 1249)
  - Awards (Box 35, Folder 1250)
- Records of theatrical productions by the Yale Rep and School of Drama, 1987-1999; Accession 2002-A-054
  - 1987-1988
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Long Day's Journey Into Night-Ah! Wilderness, Directed by Jose Quintero (Box 1)
      - The Cemetery Club, Directed by Dario Fo
  - 1988-1989
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Intermezzo, Directed by Gitta Honegger (Box 1)
      - Moon over Miami, Directed by Andrei Belgrader (Box 1)
      - Cobb (Box 1)
      - Playboy of the West Indies, Directed by Dennis Scott (Box 1)
      - Kiss of the Spider Woman, Directed by David Chambers (Box 1)
      - The Alchemist, Directed by John Hirsch (Box 1)
    - WINTERFEST IX
      - Phaedra and Hippolytus, Directed by Chris Grabowski (Box 1)
      - The Beach, Directed by Amy Saltz (Box 1)
      - Starting Monday, Directed by Peter Mark Schifter (Box 1)
      - Interrogating the Nude, Directed by Gitta Honegger (Box 1)
    - SPECIAL EVENT
      - The Warrior Ant, Directed by Lee Breuer (Box 1)
  - 1989-1990
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Solid Gold Cadillac, Directed by Gitta Honegger (Box 1)
      - Miss Julie, Directed by Dennis Scott (Box 1)
      - Summer and Smoke, Directed by Jim Simpson (Box 1)
      - Dinosaurs (Box 1)
    - WINTERFEST
      - Rust and Ruin (Box 1)
      - Pill Hill (Box 1)
      - Daylight in Exile (Box 1)
      - Dinosaurs (Box 1)
  - 1990-1991
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Ivanov, Directed by Lloyd Richards (Box 2)
      - Largo Desolato, Directed by Gitta Honegger (Box 2)
      - Scapin, Directed by Andrei Belgrader (Box 2)
      - Moon for the Misbegotten, Directed by Lloyd Richards (Box 2)
      - Ties that Bind, Directed by David Chambers (Box 2)
    - WINTERFEST IX
      - Ohio State Murders (Box 2)
      - Underground (Box 2)
  - SPECIAL EVENTS
    - 1991-1992
      - Evening with Bill Irwin (Box 2)
    - 1992-1993
      - Seven Days of Action (Box 2)
      - Theatre de la Jeune Lune (Box 2)
    - 1992-1993
      - Miscellaneous special events (Box 3)
    - 1993-1994
      - Urban Bush Women (Box 4)
      - Diamanda Galas (Box 4)
    - 1994-1995
  - 1993-1994
    - Yale School of Drama
      - Cherry Orchard, Directed by Milos Mladenovic (Box 5)
      - Love of Three Oranges, Directed Kamyar Atabi (Box 5)
      - Peer Gynt, Directed by Jean Randich (Box 5)
  - 1994-1995
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Antigone in New York, Directed by Liz Diamond (Box 5)
      - Figaro-Figaro, Directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr. (Box 5)
      - Twelfth Night, Directed by Mark Rucker (Box 5)
      - Slavs, Directed by Lisa Peterson (Box 5)
      - Uncle Vanya, Directed by Len Jenkin (Box 5)
      - Yale Voices, Directed by Liz Diamond (Box 5)
    - Yale School of Drama
      - Three Sisters, Directed by James Bundy (Box 5)
      - Good Person of Szechwan, Directed by Derek Jones (Box 5)
      - Waiting for Godot, Directed by Connie Grappo (Box 5)
    - Special Events
      - Eric Bogosian (Box 5)
      - David Cale (Box 5)
      - Rhodessa Jones (Box 5)
  - 1995-1996
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - Le Cirque Invisible, Directed by Jean Baptiste -Thierree (Box 6)
      - Pentecost, Directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr. (Box 6)
      - Mrs. Warren's Profession, Directed by Liz Diamond (Box 6)
      - The Beaux' Strategm, Directed by Everett Quinton (Box 6)
      - Venus, Directed by Richard Foreman (Box 6)
      - Landscape of the Body, Directed by Mark Rucker (Box 6)
    - Yale School of Drama
      - Diva Studies (Box 6)
      - Art of Success (Box 6)
      - Pilgrim of the Night (Box 6)
  - 1996-1997
    - Yale Repretory Theatre
      - First Lady, Directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr. (Box 7)
      - Cryptogram, Directed by Mark Rucker (Box 7)
      - Triumph of Love, Directed by Michael Mayer (Box 7)
      - Skin of our Teeth, Directed by Liz Diamond (Box 7)
      - Amy Boch, Directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr. (Box 7)
      - Thunder Knocking, Directed by Reggie Montgomery (Box 7)
    - Yale School of Drama
      - The Pope and the Witch, Directed by Dario Fo (Box 7)
      - Ride Across Lake Constance, Directed by Andrew Utter (Box 7)
      - Trojan Women, Directed by Laura Stribling (Box 7)
      - Happy End, Directed by Eleanor Holdridge (Box 7)
- Records of the managing director's office, circa 1993-2001; Accession 2004-A-087
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - AEA BOND INFO, 1998-2002 (Box 1)
  - AEA CORRESPONDANCE (Box 1)
  - BUDGET, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - CASTING, -2001 (Box 1)
  - LORT CONF, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - SHOW FILES, 1999-2000 (Box 2–4)
  - MISC DEVO-GRANT FILES (Box 4)
  - COMMERCIAL TRANSFERS -AUGUST WILSON (Box 5–6)
  - WALK INTO THE WOODS - ROAD TO MECCA (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluations
    - 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 8)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - 1997 (Box 8)
    - 1998 (Box 8)
    - 1999 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 8)
- Records documenting activities of the Yale School of Drama, circa 1926-1960s; Accession 2007-A-101
  - Expense records, 1926-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Log of ABC-Yale TV screen writing class, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University Theatre stage door log, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Technical Theatre
    - Reports, 1920s-1930s (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Student assignments, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Play reports (foreign) and translations, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Yale School of Drama productions, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Unproduced television script, "From the Patriarch to J. B.", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - History of the Department of Drama, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Alumni info, 1925-1941, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Manual of procedure, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, circa 1920s-1960s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - News releases, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Printed material, 1928-1930, 1943-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14 - 15)
  - Student papers from Drama Professor Allardyce Nicoll's criticism class
    - 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 16 - 18)
    - 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 19 - 20)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 21 - 22)
    - 1941 (Box 3, Folder 23 - 24)
  - Yale School of Drama production programs
    - Scrapbooks of programs, 1921-1940 (Box 4, Folder 25 - 27)
    - Individual programs, 1925-1969 (Box 5, Folder 28 - 38)
  - Yale Dramat programs, 1922-1967 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous programs, invitation, notice, 1927- 1957 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Lists of Yale School of Drama productions, 1925-1929 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Records of theatrical productions at the Yale Rep and Yale School of Drama, 1970-1992; Accession 2008-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1974-1975
    - Reviews (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Dolls House, 1982-1983
    - Opening (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Research (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Programs (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Memo-Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hello and Goodbye, 1982-1983
  - Opening (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Programs (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Philanderer, 1982-1983
    - Opening (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Research (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Programs (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1982-1983
    - Opening (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Programs (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - About Face, 1982-1983
    - Programs (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Memo-Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A Touch of the Poet, 1982-1983
    - Opening (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Programs (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Major Barbara, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Programs (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - A Raisin In the Sun, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Research (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Programs (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Richard II, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Research (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Programs (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Night is Mother to the Day, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Research (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Programs (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Reviews (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Programs (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - The Road to Mecca, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Programs (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Tartuffe, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Programs (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Marketing (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Henry IV Part I, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Programs (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Study Guide (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Fences, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Programs (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Clippings-NYC (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - A Play of Giants, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Research (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Program (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Marketing (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - What The Butler Saw, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Program (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Talley's Folly, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Program (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Marketing (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1981-1982
    - Opening (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1981-1982
    - Opening (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1981-1982
    - Opening (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Johnny Bull, 1981-1982
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Master Herold and the Boys, 1981-1982
    - Opening (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Research (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Love's Labor's Lost, 1981-1982
    - Opening (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 123)